Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
Wait.
انتظر.
Oh?
أوه؟
Ms. Rose.
السيدة روز.
You're early today.
لقد أتيت مبكرا اليوم.
Musheng didn't come home all night.
لم يعود موشينغ إلى المنزل طوال الليل.
I'm worried.
أنا قلق.
Move aside.
تنحى جانبا.
I'll take you to him.
سوف آخذك إليه.
This way.
من هنا.
Musheng.
موشينج.
Musheng!
موشينج!
You're a lucky man.
أنت رجل محظوظ.
Look.
ينظر.
Ms. Rose brought some porridge for you.
لقد جلبت لك السيدة روز بعض العصيدة.
Uh…
أوه…
Liu,
ليو،
I made plenty.
لقد صنعت الكثير.
Why don't you have some too?
لماذا لا يكون لديك بعضًا أيضًا؟
I don't like porridge.
انا لا احب العصيدة.
You two enjoy it.
استمتعوا بها.
How
كيف
is he?
هل هو؟
Rushed him to the hospital. He's alive, but still unconscious.
أُسرعنا به إلى المستشفى. هو على قيد الحياة، لكنه لا يزال فاقدًا للوعي.
Well, I'm full.
حسنا، أنا ممتلئ.
I'll head back now.
سأعود الآن.
What's going on with you lately?
ماذا يحدث معك في الآونة الأخيرة؟
You didn't come home last night.
لم تأتي إلى المنزل الليلة الماضية.
Let me lie on your lap.
دعني أستلقي في حضنك.
I was just too tired.
لقد كنت متعبًا جدًا.
I feel much better.
أشعر بتحسن كبير.
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
How's Tan Fei?
كيف حال تان في؟
Still unconscious.
لا يزال فاقدًا للوعي.
We don't know when he'll wake up.
نحن لا نعلم متى سوف يستيقظ.
Keep an eye
ابقي عينك
on this matter.
في هذا الشأن.
Don't worry, Boss.
لا تقلق يا رئيس.
I'm more anxious about it than you.
أنا أكثر قلقا بشأن هذا الأمر منك.
Before he bit his tongue…
قبل أن يعض لسانه…
Get out!
اخرج!
I'll leave you two to it.
سأترككما لذلك.
Answer me.
يجيبني.
Did you give me to that Japanese man?
هل أعطيتني لهذا الرجل الياباني؟
Don't get angry.
لا تغضب.
You enjoy
انت تستمتع
the chamber's benefits,
فوائد الغرفة،
so you should be ready
لذلك يجب أن تكون مستعدًا
to give something back when needed.
إعطاء شيء ما عندما تكون هناك حاجة إليه.
And if I refuse?
وإذا رفضت؟
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
If you refuse,
إذا رفضت،
then there's no place for you here.
إذن فلا مكان لك هنا.
Think it over.
فكر في الأمر.
(Du Hongyue,)
(دو هونغيو،)
(you'll get what's coming!)
(سوف تحصل على ما هو قادم!)
Get out!
اخرج!
Yamamoto caught Tan Fei
ياماموتو يمسك تان في
and handed him to Du Hongyue.
وسلمه إلى دو هونغ يوي.
Do you think he'll give you up?
هل تعتقد أنه سوف يتخلى عنك؟
He won't.
لن يفعل ذلك.
He bit his tongue
لقد عض لسانه
right in front of me.
أمامي مباشرة.
He's got guts.
لقد حصل على الشجاعة.
I have to find a way to get him out.
يجب أن أجد طريقة لإخراجه.
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Xu.
شو.
Right.
يمين.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
I saw Yamamoto take Man Li to the Yangtze Hotel.
لقد رأيت ياماموتو يأخذ مان لي إلى فندق يانغتسي.
You sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Yamamoto drugged her
ياماموتو أعطاها مخدرًا
and tried to assault her.
وحاول الاعتداء عليها.
That scumbag!
هذا الوغد!
Then what happened?
ثم ماذا حدث؟
Hong and I saved her,
لقد أنقذتها أنا وهونغ.
and we left Yamamoto
وتركنا ياماموتو
a little surprise of our own.
مفاجأة صغيرة من جانبنا.
I'm glad it all turned out fine.
أنا سعيد لأن كل شيء أصبح على ما يرام.
I can't believe they'd do that.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنهم سيفعلون ذلك.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Feeling sorry for her?
هل تشعر بالأسف عليها؟
I…
أنا…
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
Man Li
مان لي
might be spoiled,
قد تكون مدللة
but she's not a bad person deep down.
لكنها ليست شخصًا سيئًا في أعماقها.
Are you
أنت
jealous?
غيور؟
Yes.
نعم.
I am.
أنا أكون.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You're my man.
أنت رجلي.
I love seeing you jealous.
أحب رؤيتك غيورًا.
Well,
حسنًا،
you can only love me in this lifetime.
لا يمكنك أن تحبني إلا في هذه الحياة.
Got it,
فهمتها،
Zhou Musheng?
تشو موشينغ؟
Not just this life.
ليس هذه الحياة فقط.
The next,
التالي،
the one after that, and the one after that,
الذي بعده، والذي بعده،
I'll only love you.
سأحبك فقط.
Ms. Rose. Please make yourself comfortable.
آنسة روز، من فضلكِ، خذي راحتك.
I'll be done soon.
سوف أنتهي قريبا.
All right.
حسنًا.
Come back for it in two days.
عودوا إليه بعد يومين.
Ms. Rose,
السيدة روز،
Here to pick up Mr. Zhou's clothes again?
هل أنت هنا لالتقاط ملابس السيد تشو مرة أخرى؟
Yes.
نعم.
You're a good girl.
أنت فتاة جيدة.
Mr. Zhou
السيد تشو
is a blessed man.
هو رجل مبارك.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
I'll get going, then.
سأذهب إذن.
(Tan Fei's injured and in captivity)
(تان فاي مصاب وهو في الأسر)
How is he?
كيف حاله؟
Badly hurt.
مصاب بشدة.
He's still in critical condition.
مازال في حالة حرجة.
Do whatever it takes.
افعل كل ما يلزم.
He has to stay alive.
يتوجب عليه أن يبقى على قيد الحياة.
We'll do our best.
سنبذل قصارى جهدنا.
Yao.
لهم.
What did the doctor say?
ماذا قال الطبيب؟
He said a bunch of stuff I didn't get.
لقد قال مجموعة من الأشياء التي لم أفهمها.
But basically, he's done for.
لكن في الأساس، لقد انتهى أمره.
Luo Zhenyao!
لوه تشن ياو!
So this is where you've been hiding, you scum!
إذن هذا هو المكان الذي كنت تختبئ فيه، أيها الحثالة!
- Come with me! - Wait, Man Li…
- تعال معي! - انتظر يا رجل لي...
You can talk things through.
يمكنك التحدث عن الأمور.
Stay out of this.
ابقى خارج هذا .
Don't you dare follow us!
لا تجرؤ على متابعتنا!
Wait…
انتظر…
I can explain!
أستطيع أن أشرح!
Man Li,
مان لي,
let me go!
دعني أذهب!
People are watching!
الناس يراقبون!
Did you
هل فعلت؟
spike my drink?
هل أضيف مادة إلى مشروبي؟
You saw me do it?
هل رأيتني أفعل ذلك؟
Who else
من غيره
would use such filthy tricks?
هل يستخدم مثل هذه الحيل القذرة؟
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
I was just following orders.
لقد كنت فقط أتبع الأوامر.
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار.
Whose orders?
أوامر من؟
Du Hongyue's?
دو هونغيو؟
I didn't say that.
لم اقل ذلك
Man Li,
مان لي,
you've been
لقد كنت
risking your life for him
المخاطرة بحياتك من أجله
for years,
لسنوات،
and now
والآن
he sells you out
هو يبيعك
to please the Japanese.
لإرضاء اليابانيين.
Even I feel sorry
حتى أنا أشعر بالأسف
for you.
لك.
You think you're any better?
هل تعتقد أنك أفضل؟
You've been by his side all these years too.
لقد كنت بجانبه كل هذه السنوات أيضًا.
Do you see your name
هل ترى اسمك
on his right-hand list?
على قائمته اليمنى؟
If he'd betray me,
لو خانني،
he'll betray you
سوف يخونك
too…
أيضاً…
That's why
لهذا السبب
we should work together
ينبغي علينا أن نعمل معا
to maximize our mutual interests.
لتعظيم مصالحنا المتبادلة.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
give Luo Zhenyao the note
أعط Luo Zhenyao المذكرة
with my name.
مع اسمي.
Tell them
أخبرهم
I'm your contact.
أنا جهة الاتصال الخاصة بك.
No.
لا.
That's too dangerous for you.
هذا خطير جدًا بالنسبة لك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I can handle myself.
أنا قادر على التعامل مع نفسي.
Senior…
كبير…
Take care…
يعتني…
You too.
أنت أيضاً.
Whatever you decide,
مهما كان قرارك،
I'll back you up.
سأدعمك.
So
لذا
that's a yes?
هذا نعم؟
Deal.
اتفاق.
Pleasure working with you.
يسعدني العمل معك.
So…
لذا…
How about drinks at my place tonight?
ماذا عن المشروبات في مكاني الليلة؟
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Hey.
يا.
You two done fighting?
هل إنتهيتم من القتال؟
Just talk it out. We're on the same side.
فقط تحدثوا. نحن على نفس الجانب.
Yeah, yeah, we're all good now.
نعم، نعم، نحن جميعا بخير الآن.
Just a misunderstanding.
مجرد سوء فهم.
Right, Man Li?
يمينًا، مان لي؟
Then I'll get going,
ثم سأذهب
Yao.
لهم.
(They've made up already?)
(لقد تصالحوا بالفعل؟)
(Those two are definitely up to something.)
(من المؤكد أن هذين الشخصين يخططان لشيء ما.)
Pomegranates! Plump and sweet pomegranates!
رمان! رمان ممتلئ ولذيذ!
Hello, Miss.
مرحباً يا آنسة.
Would you like some pomegranates? They're sweet.
هل ترغب ببعض الرمان؟ إنه حلو.
Try one.
جرب واحدة.
Yi, have one.
يي، لدي واحدة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Pack a few
حزمة قليلة
for me.
لي.
All right.
حسنًا.
How much?
كم ثمن؟
Two copper coins.
عملتين نحاسيتين.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
(Night Shanghai)
(ليلة شنغهاي)
Man Li.
مان لي.
Hey.
يا.
Rose.
وَردَة.
Were you looking for me?
هل كنت تبحث عني؟
No.
لا.
I was just passing by.
لقد كنت أمر فقط.
Oh.
أوه.
Did you just get off work?
هل خرجت للتو من العمل؟
Yes.
نعم.
I just got off work.
لقد خرجت للتو من العمل.
Want
يريد
to grab a drink together?
لتناول مشروب معًا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm free tonight.
أنا متفرغ الليلة.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Let's go.
- دعنا نذهب.
What are you doing around here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Just picking up a few things.
فقط التقط بعض الأشياء.
Well, if it isn't Night Shanghai's Rose.
حسنًا، إذا لم تكن وردة شنغهاي الليلية.
Where are you headed?
إلى أين أنت متجه؟
Go away.
يبتعد.
You go away!
أنت تذهب بعيدا!
Man Li!
مان لي!
Let's have
دعونا نملك
a drink together.
مشروبًا معًا.
Let…
يترك…
Let's not go home until we're drunk…
لا نعود إلى المنزل حتى نكون في حالة سُكر...
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
It's a misunderstanding…
إنه سوء فهم
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I didn't scare you, did I?
لم أخفك، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪